Guide to the Ithaca Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender Task Force records, 1984-2005.
Ithaca Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender Task Force records,
- Series XII. Original Layouts
  - Summer 1996--Outlines--originals (Removed ads: Yahn page 11; Morris page 5 [used on Fall 1996]; Common Ground page 32 [used on Winter 1996]) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Fall 1996--Outlines--originals (Removed ads: STAP page 21; Yahn page 23 [used on Winter 1996]) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Winter 1996--Outlines--originals (Removed: STAP ad page 8 [used on Spring 1997]) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Spring 1997--Outlines--originals (Removed Ads for Summer 1997: First Baptist page 12; Heartwood page 21; Barringer page 31; Foree page 17; STAP page 26) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Summer 1997--Outlines--originals (Removed ads for Fall 1997 issue: Cayuga Fitness Center page 12; Barringer page 34; First Baptist page 5; Foree page 22; Milner page 15; Planned Parenthood page 3; Saunders page 34; STAP page 28) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Outlines issues with editorial notes from Migdalia Valdes, 1980s (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Series XIII. Big Red Rag
  - The Big Red Rag, Winter 1987/1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Outlines Rought Draft Layouts (hand drawn), No Date (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Big Red Rag Rough Draft Layouts (hand drawn), No Date (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Series XIV. ILGBTF Flyers/Mailings
  - Not Your Mom's Prom (Gaypril 4 9pm to 1am Ithaca Youth Bureau), April (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ages and Stages in the Lives of Lesbian, Gays and Bisexuals, April 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Letter to citizens of Ithaca who will cote in three new members of the Ithaca School Board, May 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ithaca Lesbian Gay Bisexual Task Force Mailings, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Ithaca Lesbian Gay Bisexual Task Force Mailings, 1996-1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Ithaca Lesbian Gay Bisexual Transgender Task Force Mailings, September 2005 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1974 Clipping and July 4th Coalition Newsletter (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Series XV. Oversize
  - March Perspectives: Taking it to the Streets (March on Washington October 11, 1987), October 1987 (Mapcase-folder 1)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
The following materials have been cataloged separately:
Act Up Reports, June 1989.
Baltimore Gaypaper, May, June, September, and October 1989.
The Empty Closet, April 1989.
Gay Community News, July 1989.
Hera, August 1989.
Living In Leather, 1989.
Outlines, February/March 1987, February/March/April 1988, Winter Eternal (1988), February/March 1989, April/May 1989, Summer 1989, September 1989, December 1991.
The Washington Blade, November 1989.